# George Boholteanu

# Software Developer

I am a software developer based in London with a curios mind in learning about new technologies and self development. Drawing from my background in Architecture and Visualization, where I focused on delivering exceptional user experiences through ultra-realistic graphics or CGIs, I am excited to enhance my software development knowledge to create well-rounded, user-centric applications.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



## \*\*Web Developer - PROFILETREE\*\* (Sep 2023 - Present)

- Conducted in-depth competitor analysis for a comprehensive career guidance app presenting findings to leadership.
- Wireframing landing page using Figma
- Web Designing using Wordpress to create landing page and a quizz application.

## \*\*Front End Developer - EDX Trilogy\*\* (Nov 2022 - Mar 2023)

- Developed a series of web applications utilizing Agile methodologies.
- Proficient in HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, React and Node.js.
- Created a Freelancer Booking App, a Trivia App using Trivia API and GIPHY API, Personal Portfolio, and a Weather Dashboard using Openweather API.

#### \*\*Software Developer - Self Development\*\* (Mar 2020 - Present)

- Portfolio app using NextJs, TypeScript, React, Vercel and Framer Motion
- Web design for a Fitness Club. Node-Sequelize Cloud Authentication App
- Designed and developed a Python-based Smart Assets Manager UI for data organization and web scraping.
- Conducted web scraping and data wrangling for Premier League match results using Python.
- Created animated data visualizations using Flourish App and developed UI tools in 3D Studio Max for automation.

#### \*\*Lead 3D Visualizer - Freelance\*\* (February 2020 - Present)

- Produced marketing CGIs for clients like HENLEY Real Estates Investments and WESTWAY Architects.
- Led client meetings, translated their vision into design proposals, and managed project timelines.

### \*\*Architectural Visualizer - AHMM Architects\*\* (Apr 2017 - Pres)

- Established an efficient content management system, automating asset processes. Introduced a content library for streamlined design, alleviating repetitive tasks.
- Solved recurring visualization issues within the R&D team
- Delivered a variety of CGIs for design decision-making.
- Provided mentorship and guidance to junior visualizers.

#### \*\*3D Visualizer - Foster and Partners\*\* (Sept 2014 - Apr 2017)

- Collaborated with senior visualizers to produce outstanding CGIs for clients worldwide on high-profile projects.



### London, UK | +447759311139

george.boholteanu@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/georgeboholteanu-638957267/

https://webdev-portfolio-navy.vercel.app/

# SKILLS (

- Programming: Python, React, JavaScript, Typescript, NextJS
- Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Figma, **Express**
- Version Control: Git
- Tools: 3D Studio Max. Photoshop, Illustrator
- Data Visualization: Flourish App
- **Soft Skills**: Problem-solving, creativity, adaptability, effective communication, collaboration. leadership, continuous learning, empathy.

# EDUCATION 🔀



\*\*EDX Trilogy\*\*

Front End Web Development Bootcamp\*\* (Mar 2023)

# \*\*SOLOLEARN COURSES\*\*

- Python for Data Science Course (Dec 2021)
- Python Intermediate Course (Dec
- SQL Course (Nov 2021)

## \*\*Univ. of Architecture, **Bucharest, Romania\*\***

Master in Architectural Design (Jul 2014)

### **INTERESTS**

- Technology
- Sports
- Self Development